atu2.com 2019-05-09

# Privacy Policy

@U2 is created by U2 fans for U2 fans. Your privacy is important to us, and we provide this privacy policy to inform you how and when we may collect personal information from you, and what we do with that information.

By registering an account or using the site, you are signifying your acceptance of this privacy policy. If you don’t agree with this policy, please do not use our site.

 **Personal Information**

When you register an account on the site or use the site to contact us, we collect personal information that you voluntarily share with us and use it only for the purpose of providing services on this web site. These services may include a tool for listing which U2 concerts you've seen and which songs were performed at those concerts, a tool for allowing you to publish reviews and/or photos of the U2 concerts you've seen, a tool that will tell you about upcoming U2-related events in your time zone, a fan forum/message board where you can post messages in conversation with other U2 fans, and so forth. We may use your personal information to contact you if you or we discover issues arising from your use of the web site. We will never share or sell your personal information with a third party.

 **Anonymous Information**

Like most web sites, we also collect anonymous information about how you use our web site. The data we collect may include IP addresses, the names of pages you visit, how long you spend on the site, etc. Our analytics program(s) collects and presents this data in the aggregate; it doesn’t include any personally identifiable information. We review and use this data to understand our site visitors’ preferences and improve our web site and the services we offer.

 **Questions?**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at any time.
